Mohat Shil

QA AUTOMATION ENGINEER **A**

Personal Landing Page: https://mohat.vercel.app/

Work style/Pull-request: https://github.com/reactplay/react-play/pull/1481

Szlak 41, 5/A Krakow, 31-161 +48 576727596 2850542@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

As a QA Automation Engineer with 5 years of experience in web and mobile application testing, I possess extensive knowledge of Typescript/Javascript, test automation frameworks such as Playwright/Puppeteer/WebdriverIO/Cypress, and various testing tools including Jenkins/OWASP. My academic credentials include a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science with a major in Quality Engineering and a minor in Cloud Engineering.

EXPERIENCE

ABB, Poland — *QA Automation Engineer*

OCTOBER 2023 - PRESENT

SAFe team collaboration, Maintaining AQA structure, Maintaining large scaled automation repository, generating E2E tests proactively, running pipelines regularly, pair programming, knowledge transfer, evaluating a11y tests periodically, gathering/discussing valuable test artifact(s) are some of my key responsibilities in this position.

EPAM Systems, Poland — Senior Software Test Engineer

MAY 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2023

Scrum team collaboration, Requirements gathering, Acceptance criteria, Test planning, Stakeholder sign-off, Functional testing, Non-functional testing, Bug detection, Error reporting, Defect tracking, Communication, Risk management & Test improvements were some of my key responsibilities in this position.

Keywords Studios, Poland — QA Lead

JULY 2021 - APRIL 2022

Project management, Workflow integration, Leadership, Team management, Communication, Feedback, Performance evaluation were some of my key responsibilities in this position.

Testronic Labs, Poland — Associate Lead

OCTOBER 2018 - JUNE 2021

Security procedures, Policy adherence, Test design, Mentoring, Task completion, Best practices, Line management, Staff evaluation, Client communication, duties & Time monitoring were some of my key responsibilities in this position.

EDUCATION

Vistula University, Poland — Bachelors, Computer Science

JANUARY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2021 Major: Quality Engineering

SKILLS

Test Automation Framework

Testing Fundamentals

Agile Fundamentals (SCRUM)

CI/CD Fundamentals

UI E2E Testing | API Testing

BDD/TDD Fundamentals

A11y Testing

POM/OOP model using - DRY/KISS

Test Estimation

Performance Test Fundamentals

TECH STACK

Playwright (JS/TS) ~ 3yrs

Cypress (JS/TS) ~ 2yrs

WebDriver IO (JS/TS) ~ 1yrs

Jenkins | BASH | Postman

Docker | Kubernetes

Azure DevOps | Jira

JMeter | OWASP

Basic Python

LANGUAGES

English - C1+ Bangla - Native